NARRATION: You open the door and come face to face with a young brunette girl wearing glasses. She has a friendly smile.

Emelia: Hi! I'm Emelia. I just came by to welcome you.

MC: Thanks.

Emelia: I heard you're the one who graduated from college.

Ariz: I mean of course you would be since you're the first person who moved here since a few months back.

MC: That's right. I graduated with a Bachelors's in Magic Arts. So I guess you can officially call me a caster now.

Emelia: Really? That's really cool! Do you have a casting glove? You should have one.

MC: Yeah but it got damaged during the move.

Emelia: Oh that's unfortunate. How did it happen?

MC: I guess it must have hit something pretty hard while the truck was driving around.

Emelia: I think it could be fixed. I know someone who repairs them.

MC: Really?

Emelia: Yeah there's a workshop. I can take you there if you like.

MC: Great! I'll get ready.